BRYAN WILSON

bryan@brianwithay.com

<u>brianwithay.com</u> (937) 716-7285

ABOUT

Quality Assurance Analyst with over two years of manual and automated testing experience and over four years of experience with data analysis and visualization. Bryan is skilled at each level of the project lifecycle, from requirements and objective planning to testing and reporting.

EDUCATION

BS, Management Information Systems Wright State University

SKILLS

Advanced: Manual Testing, Test Case Management, Business Analysis, Specification Writing, Data Analysis and Visualization

Intermediate: Automated Testing, SEO Analysis, HTML/CSS, JS/Node.js, Java, Digital Ad Campaigns, Load Testing

TOOLS I'VE WORKED WITH

Jira, Selenium, Java, Nightwatch.js, Katalon, Tableau, RapidMiner, NoSQL/ MySQL/MSSQL, Sitefinity, Wordpress, Postman, Google Analytics, Google Adwords and more.

References available upon request...

EMPLOYMENT

QUALITY ASSURANCE ANALYST Real Art Design Group

2016 - Present Dayton, OH

- Performed manual and automated testing for web, mobile, VR/AR and client
- Managed test cases, bug reporting/project planning systems and specifications
- Analyzed and visualized data for internal and client use
- Hands-on at all phases of project development including design and functional review

TECHNICAL DIRECTOR Integrity Water Solutions, LLC.

2010 - Present Beavercreek, OH

- Developed and maintain company website
- Support all networks, workstations, mobile devices and POS systems
- Provide business guidance and support as needed
- Led the branding and social initiative through training and material creation

WINDOWS ENTERPRISE SYSTEMS CO-OP Lexis Nexis

2015 - 2016 Miamisburg, OH

- Created IT service tools allowing level 2 service tasks to be automated
- Performed business analysis duties for a Windows Server 2003 upgrade project
- Performed QA testing on Citrix and HP Operations Manager upgrade projects
- Developed and maintained customer-facing support and Sharepoint site

CERTIFICATIONS

Google Analytics - June 2016 - Present

Google Adwords - May 2018 - Present

Microsoft MTA - IT Infrastructure - August 2015 - Present

Microsoft MTA - Database - August 2015 - Present